{
    "subject": "resource/The_Long_Ryders",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The Long Ryders are from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.834280788898468,
            "question": "Are there any famous bands from the United States besides The Long Ryders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8052359223365784,
            "question": "Where are The Long Ryders from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6067222356796265,
            "question": "What country is The Long Ryders associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4523579478263855,
            "question": "When were The Long Ryders popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4465194046497345,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about The Long Ryders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4095168709754944,
            "question": "Is The Long Ryders a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3492515981197357,
            "question": "What is the musical genre of The Long Ryders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.343594491481781,
            "question": "What is the cultural significance of The Long Ryders?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22985601425170898,
            "question": "Who are some other musicians from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18986539542675018,
            "question": "Are there any famous musicians from The United States?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Long Ryders are from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9062_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some other musicians from the United States?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9062_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the cultural significance of The Long Ryders?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9062_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the musical genre of The Long Ryders?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9062_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9062_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that The Long Ryders are an \"American rock \u2018n roll band\" and were formed in Los Angeles, California.  This indicates they are from the United States."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that The Long Ryders are an American band. According to the documents, they were formed in Los Angeles, California (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9062/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt), and their members were American musicians influenced by Gram Parsons, C&W, The Byrds, and the punk scene (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_9062/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently refer to The Long Ryders as an American band, which supports the statement that they are from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}